pageone.ph 2018-06-15

# Privacy Policy – PAGEONE

PageOne.ph is a website that is developed and managed by PAGEONE MEDIA & COMMUNICATIONS PHILIPPINES, Inc. 

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices of PageOne.ph. This website wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, and as such we disclose our information and user privacy practices.

**A. Information We Collect and Receive**

We collect and receive information about you and your device when you give it to us directly, when you use our Services, and from certain third-party sources.

**B. Cookies**

PageOne.ph itself occasionally makes use of cookies. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. However, since cookies can enable websites to track and target the interests of its users to enhance the experience on the site, we may sometimes make use of cookies.

**C. Information Usage**

When PageOne.ph holds surveys or promos, you may be required to input your contact information (such as name, e-mail address or mobile number) and demographic information (such as income level, gender etc.). This information is used to contact you about the services on our site for which you have expressed interest or to inform you if you won in a certain contest or promo. It is optional for you to provide and unique identifiers (such as social security number or driver’s license number).

**C. Information Sharing**

PageOne.ph shall only share aggregated information with our partners and advertisers for the sole purpose of identifying the websites’ visitor demographics. These information are not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

**D. Notification of changes**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by e-mail. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
